aiyellow.com 2014-06-27

# 

PRIVACY POLICY
Effective: November 2012
AMARILLASINTERNET CORPORATION - PRIVACY POLICY
INTRODUCTION
COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION
COLLECTION AND SHARING OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
AGGREGATING INFORMATION
COOKIES – TRACKING COOKIES
THIRD PARTY INFORMATION
CHILDREN’S PRVACY PROTECTION
CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER
RETENTION
This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way AmarillasInternet Corporation,
(hereinafter jointly and/or severally referred to as “AiYellow” or we”), uses and protects
the information we collect about Members, Customers and Users. This Privacy Policy
applies to all use, products, and services offered by AiYellow, as well as visits to our
websites including any and all AiYellow-branded URL’s (the “AiYellow Website”), and
any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by AiYellow in
connection with the AiYellow Website. AiYellow may modify this Privacy Policy to
reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law; your continued use of the AiYellow
Services after AiYellow posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the
revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy
regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If AiYellow materially changes
its practices regarding collection or use of your, Personally identifiable information,
You will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless You
have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.
COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION "PII";
We collect information such as your full name, user name, postal address (including
billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, e-mail address, or credit card
number; information that members voluntarily provide to AiYellow when you choose to
participate in our offers and programs or otherwise provide information directly to us,
including when you register with us, purchase products, participate in our interactive
features or otherwise interact with us on AiYellow Site.
AiYellow may use PII: to send you information about your affiliation or transactions
with us; to tell you about products, services, programs, and offers that we believe may
be of interest to you via, telephone, Cell phone, postal mail, e-mail or SMS; to allow
you to use, communicate and interact with others on our Site; to help you find an
Independent Sales affiliate; for AiYellow internal business purposes, such as data
analysis, audits, new products, enhancing our website, improving our services,
identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional
campaigns; to allow you to send an e-mail to other people through our Website.
SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION;
AiYellow do not sell trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable
Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any PII you provide to
us will be stored in our database. Except companies that are affiliated with the AiYellow
family.

AiYellow may disclose your PII; to third-party service providers who provide services to
AiYellow, such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment,
infrastructure provision, information technology services, customer service, e-mail
delivery services, credit card processing, auditing, training, and other similar services.
(These third parties will be supplied with, or have access to, your Personal Information
for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf); to the extent
necessary for them to contact you, fulfill your orders or a third party in the event of any
reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of
all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any
bankruptcy or similar proceedings); and as we believe necessary or appropriate: (a)
under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply
with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities
including public and government authorities outside your country of residence.
COLLECTION AND SHARING OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION;
When visitors come to our site, we may collect information indicating, among other
things, which pages were visited, the order in which they were visited and which
hyperlinks were clicked. Collecting such information involves visitor’s logging of IP
addresses, operating system, browser software, Internet Service Provider, and
geographic location. The non-personally identifiable information we gather helps us,
among others things, to monitor our internal operations, improve our services, identify
the most popular areas of our site and determine the effectiveness of our services and
promotional activities. It also helps us to improve our available online services to
assure they are high-quality and useful. We acquire this by performing statistical
analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of the users, and by measuring
demographics and interests regarding specific areas of our site. We provide statistical
information based on this data to advertisers and to current and potential promotional
partners. Because Non-Personal Information does not personally identify you, we may
collect, use and disclose Non-Personal Information for any purpose.
AGGREGATING INFORMATION;
We may aggregate Personal Information so that the aggregated information does not
personally identify you or anyone else, such as by using Personal Information to
calculate the percentage of our customers who live in a particular area. In some
instances, we may combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such
as combining your name with your geographical location). If we combine any Non-
Personal Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be
treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined.
DATA PROTECTION AND SECURITY;
AiYellow do not sell your Personal Information to anyone for any purpose. We maintain
information about you in our business records while you are a Member, advertiser,
costumer, user or until it is no longer needed for business, tax, or legal purposes. We
have implemented encryption or other appropriate security controls to protect Personal
Information when stored or transmitted by AiYellow Team. We require non-AiYellow
companies acting on our behalf to protect any Personal Information they may receive
in a manner consistent with this Policy.
COOKIES – TRACKING COOKIES;
A “cookie” (also known as web cookie, browser cookie, HTTP cookie, and tracking
cookie) is a recourse that allows our service to identify users. AiYellow sends a
“cookie” to the computer on the first visit. This allows us to serve visitors of our site
better and more efficiently.

Cookies are small text files placed on a visitor’s computer’s hard drive if permitted by
the browser. Cookies, among other things, make it easier to access our sites and
services, and help us track the pages that visitors go to, determine the length of time
visitors spend at any particular are of the site and track the services visitors choose to
use. Cookies can only be read by the server that placed them, and they are unable to
read data from hard disks, execute any code, send viruses or destroy files. For
information on how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser, please
refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.
CHILDREN’S PRVACY PROTECTION;
Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under legal age, and we will
not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover
personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data. You must be at
least 18 years old to qualify as An Adveritser, Member, or Customers to be on our Site.
CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER;
Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have
operations, and by interacting with us and providing us with any Personal Information,
you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of
residence, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection
rules than in your country.
THIRD PARTY INFORMATION;
If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving information from promotional
partners, please contact those third parties directly and let them know your decision.
Otherwise, contact at: legal@aiyellow.com and we will advise such parties that you
wish to discontinue receiving their promotional information. Nevertheless, the Company
takes no responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, or the way in which
they use information received either from www.aiyellow.com, or independently
RETENTION;
We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes
outlined in this Privacy Statement unless a longer retention period is required or
allowed by law.
This Statement ©2012 AmarillasInternet Corporation. All rights reserved.
